6/28:
The scope of my desires for this project is getting out of hand, and I am
having fun writting down new text documents in VIM, so here is braindump of my
desires for this project: 

1. Get a better IDE set up, so that you are comfortable debugging and playing
around with these different functions. As programmers go, you are an
experimentalist. You learn (and remember) aspects of a program better if you
can experiment with them.

2. Although copy and pasting karpathy's code is fun and all, there is little
learning done in that process. I should accept that the day-to-day coding
process may require my to be a little bit less on auto-pilot.

3. Talk to someone about this stuff. I have learned a lot in this last week,
but it doesn't feel like it throughout most of the day because no one else in
my world recognizes it. Or else, find a way to make your new insights
meaningfull without the reliance on interactions with others. 

4. Learn from karpthy's code!
	- the different ways to represent, translate, and compute data (bits,
	  hex, base-58 encoding
	- good programming techniques
	- what tools to get better at 

5. Understand the motivations behind each of these cryptographic functions.
What is the purpose of each crytpographic funciton? How do they work? Why are
they used in the way that they are used? 

6. Look at the bigger picture of this project! What do you expect to learn and
take away from this project. How can you frame what you know in the larger
scheme of things. Is the scope and scale of what you are doing the most
effective way to meet your goals? 

7. More general reading and research on crypto.

8. Stretch your creativity! Daydream about the ideas you have encountered so
far and see if you can discover fundamental ways of thinking about them.

9. See where you have gotten so far. Go through your code, your repo, your
codex, etc. Clean up things, organize them in your mind. Tie up little loose
ends here and there. Think about how you or another person may view this
information in the future.

10. Check out karpathy's jupyter notebook post! 

11. Use this opportunity to learn things and cement your understanding of
things as much as possible. You are following in the footsteps of a great
programmer. Learn usefull tools and practices along the way (such as VIM).  

12. Analyze and refine your organization and processees. Is this codex thing
through draw.io a good way to document projects? What are the habits that are
good to a project. What are the habits that are bad to a project, (such as 
comparing yourself personally to a fricking genius) or probably more
importantly (wasting time with hyper-active introspection) ;)

"I wonder why. I wonder why. I wonder why I wonder. I wonder why I wonder why. I wonder why
I wonder!" 
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Okay, brain dump done. Below I will write notes about progress on these points
-------------------------------------------------------------------------------
blah blah 

